Guide to the William E. Irwin Photograph Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Arizona, circa 1904-1945; Series II; 1.25; (1 box)
  - Cave Creek Canyon
    - View of a rock formation in Cave Creek Canyon, Arizona, 1920 August 22; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 64)
      Inscription on recto of a print: "Cave Creek Canon, Ariz."
      Inscription on verso of a print: "Made in Cave Creek Canon, Aug. 22, 1920"
    - View of a rock formation in Cave Creek Canyon, Arizona, 1920 August 22; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - View of a meadow and trees in Cave Creek Canyon, Arizona, with mountains in the background, 1920 August 22; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 66)
      Inscription on recto of a print: "Cave Creek Canyon near Douglas, Ariz."
      Inscription on verso of a print: "Made in Cave Creek Canon, Aug. 22, 1920, near Douglas"
    - View of a rock formation in Cave Creek Canyon, Arizona, 1920 August 22; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 67)
      Inscription on recto of a print: "Scenes in Cave Creek Canyon, Ariz."
    - View in Cave Creek Canyon, Arizona, 1920 August 22; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 68)
      Inscription on verso of a print: "View in Cave Creek Canyon, Ariz., Aug. 22 - 1920"
    - View of Cave Creek Canyon, Arizona, with three women posed standing and sitting on rocks in Cave Creek, opposite camp Bonita, 1920 August 22; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 69)
      Inscription on verso of a print: "View in Cave Creek Canyon, Ariz., Aug. 22 - 1920, opposite camp Bonita"
  - Chiricahua Mountains
    - View of three men, including William Edward "Ed" Irwin aiming a rifle and two men carrying deer carcasses, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 70)
      Inscription on recto: "Deer hunting in the Chiricahua Mts., Ariz."
    - View of rock formations in Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 71)
      Inscription in negative: "Monument Park in Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Photo Irwin"
    - View of rock formations in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 72)
      Inscription in negative: "Scenes in Monument Park, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Photo Irwin"
    - View of rock formations in Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - View of rock formations in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 74)
      Inscription in negative: "Wonderland of Rocks, near Douglas, Ariz., Photo Irwin"
    - View of rock formations in Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mountains, with Cochise Head rock formation in the distance, in Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 75)
      Inscription in negative: "Cochise Head, as seen from Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Photo Irwin"
      Inscription on verso: "Notice the mountain in the distance shaped like a human face lying face upward, this accounts for the name, Cochise Head"
    - View of rock formations in Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 76)
      Inscription in negative: "Scenes in Bonita Canyon, n, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Photo Irwin"
    - View of a rock formation, identified as Balanced Rock, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 77)
      Inscription in negative: "Balanced Rock, Wonderland of Rocks, near Douglas, Ariz., Irwin, #X15"
    - View of a rock formation, identified as Balanced Rock, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 78)
      Inscription in negative: "Balanced Rock, Wonderland of Rocks, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a rock formation, identified as Mushroom Rock, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 79)
      Inscription in negative: "Mushroom Rock, Wonderland of Rocks, near Douglas, Ariz., Irwin, X3"
    - View of rock formations in Bonita Canyon, Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - View of a rock formation, identified as Natural Bridge, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 81)
      Inscription in negative: "Natural Bridge, Wonderland of Rocks, near Douglas, Ariz., Irwin, #16"
    - View of rock formations, identified as Punch and Judy, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print and 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 82)
      Inscription in negative: "Punch and Judy, Wonderland of Rocks, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a rock formation in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 83)
      Inscription in negative: "Freak Rocks in the Wonderland of Rocks, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a rock formation in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 84)
      Inscription in negative: "One of the wonders of Wonderland of Rocks, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a rock formation, identified as Balanced Rock, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 85)
      Inscription in negative: "Balanced Rock in Wonderland of Rocks, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a man posed standing next to a rock formation, identified as Mushroom, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 86)
      Inscription in negative: "Mushroom in Wonderland of Rocks, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of rock formations, identified as totem poles, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 87)
      Inscription in negative: "Totem poles in the Wonderland of Rocks, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of rock formations, identified as totem poles, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 88)
      Inscription in negative: "Totem poles, Rhyolite Park near Douglas, Ariz."
    - View of rock formation, identified as the Duck, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 89)
      Inscription in negative: "'The Duck,' Wonderland of Rocks, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of rock formations in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 90)
      Inscription in negative: "'Wonderland of Rocks, Chiricahua Mts., Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a rock formation, identified as Balanced Rock, in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, 1925 November 25; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 91)
      Inscription in negative: "'Balanced Rock, Wonderland of Rocks near Douglas, Ariz., Irwin, #118"
      Correspondence on verso from William Edward "Ed" Irwin to Minnie Pearl Irwin Mitchell
    - View of a rock formation in silhouette from a sunset, probably in the Chiricahua Mountains, Arizona, 1920 August; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 92)
      Inscription on verso: "Sunset sillouette near Douglas, Ariz., Aug. 1920"
  - Clifton
    - Exterior portrait of a woman, identified as Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin, posed standing and holding a mining hammer in a desert landscape that includes a pool of water, near Clifton, Arizona, circa 1904-1922; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 93)
      Inscription on recto: "Scene near Clifton, Ariz."
      Inscription on verso: "Tillie Irwin (W. E.)"
    - View of a rocky desert landscape with trees near Clifton, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 94)
      Inscription in the negative: "Scenes along Apache Creek near Clifton, Ariz., Irwin"
  - Douglas
    - View of a main street in Douglas, Arizona, circa 1915; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 95)
      Ink inscription on recto: "Douglas, Ariz." and "x"
      Ink inscription on verso: "where you see x, is where we have our studio"
    - View of three women mounted on horses with an additional horse near Douglas, Arizona, circa 1915; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 96)
      Inscription on recto: "Scenes near Douglas, Ariz."
    - Exterior portrait of two women, identified as Mrs. Meadows and Era Bock, posed standing with two horse near an automobile on a ranch near Douglas, Arizona, circa 1915; 3 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 97)
      Inscription on recto of a print: "Mrs. Meadows and Era, ranch scene near Douglas, Ariz."
    - View of a Fourth of July parade in Douglas, Arizona, with United States Army Cavalry troops on G Avenue, 1915? July 4; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 98)
      Correspondence on verso from Marvin Elmore Irwin to Mary Frances "Molly" Elmore Irwin, July 6th
  - Fort Thomas
    - View of yucca plants near Fort Thomas, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 99)
      Pencil inscription on verso: "Near Ft. Thomas, Ariz."
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse standing among Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1918; 1 hand colored unmounted photographic print and 3 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 100)
      Inscription in negative of all prints: "In the Cactus Lands of Ariz., Copyright 1918 by Irwin, Bisbee, Ariz."
      Inscription on the verso of a print: "Views around Ft. Thomas, Ariz."
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse standing among Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1918; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 101)
      Inscription in negative of both prints: "In the Hills of Arizona, Copyright 1918 by Irwin, Bisbee, Ariz."
    - Exterior portrait of a woman, identified as Carrie Matilda "Tillie" Allen Irwin, posed sitting on a rock and pointing at a white horse standing among Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1918; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 102)
      Inscriptions on the verso of a print: "Views around Ft. Thomas, Ariz." and "By Ed Irwin, 1702 East First St., Tucson, Arizona, Picture No. I"
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse standing among Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1918; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 103)
      Inscription in negative of both prints: "Arizona, Copyright 1918 by Irwin, Bisbee, Ariz."
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse standing among Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1918; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 104)
      Inscription in negative of both prints: "Giant Cactus of Arizona, Copyright 1918 by Irwin, Bisbee, Ariz."
      Inscriptions on the verso of a print: "Views around Ft. Thomas, Ariz." and "By Ed Irwin, 1702 E. 1st St., Tucson, Arizona, Picture No. 17"
    - Exterior portrait of a woman, identified as Minnie Pearl Irwin Mitchell, posed mounted on a dark-colored horse with another white horse nearby in a desert landscape with Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1920 August; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 105)
      Inscription on recto: "Minnie Mitchell on her way through Arizona"
      Blind-stamp on recto: "Irwin, Bisbee, Ariz."
    - Exterior portrait of a woman, identified as Minnie Pearl Irwin Mitchell, posed sitting on a boulder in a desert landscape with Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, circa 1904-1922; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - View of a Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus in a desert landscape, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, circa 1904-1922; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 107)
      Inscription on recto: "Giant cactus of Ariz."
    - Exterior portrait of a woman, identified as Minnie Pearl Irwin Mitchell, posed sitting on a boulder in a desert landscape with Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1920 August; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 108)
      Inscription on recto: "Mrs. J. H. Mitchell in the desert country of Arizona"
    - View of a white horse and dark-colored horse in a desert landscape with Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus, near Fort Thomas, Arizona, circa 1904-1922; 1 unmounted photographic print and 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 109)
      Inscription on recto of the unmounted print: "In the foothills along the Gila Riv., Ariz."
      Inscription on recto of the postcard: "Scene on Ft. Thomas Ranch, Ariz."
      Blind-stamp on recto of the unmounted print: "Irwin, Bisbee, Ariz."
    - Exterior portrait of a man, identified as William Edward "Ed" Irwin, posed standing with a white horse among Fouquieria splendens (ocotillo) cactus and yucca plants, probably near Fort Thomas, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 110)
      Inscription on recto: "Ed on Ft. Thomas Ranch, Ariz."
    - View of a flock of turkeys at Fort Thomas, Arizona, 1920 August 8; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 111)
      Inscription on verso: "Turkeys at Ft. Thomas ranch, Ariz., Aug. 8 - 1920"
    - View of four cats and a dog surrounding a gopher on a ranch in Fort Thomas, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 112)
      Inscription on recto: "The gopher holding his own!"
      Inscriptions on verso: "On the Ranch at Ft. Thomas, Ariz.," "The gopher holding his own!," "By Ed Irwin, 1702 E. 1st St., Tucson, Ariz., Picture #20"
  - Gila River
    - View of goats on the banks of the Gila River in Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 113)
      Inscription on verso: "Gila, Ariz."
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse and Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus near the Gila River, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 114)
      Inscription in negative: "Scenes in the foot hills along the Gila River, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse and Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus near the Gila River, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 2 photographic postcards (Box 2, Folder 115)
      Inscription in negative: "In the foot hills along the Gila River, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of a desert landscape with a white horse and Carnegiea gigantea (saguaro) cactus near the Gila River, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - View of the Gila River in Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 117)
      Inscription on verso: "Gila River, Ariz."
    - View of the Gila River and rocky hills in Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 118)
      Inscription in negative: "Along the Gila River on the Coronado Trail, Photo by Irwin"
    - View of a dirt road parallel to the Gila River in Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print
      Related Archival Materials note
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 905
      Inscription in negative: "Along the Lordsburg Clifton Highway on the Gila River, Ariz., Photo by Irwin"
  - Guadalupe Canyon
    - Overhead view of a hunting camp with a wall tent, two women, and three men in Guadalupe Canyon, Arizona, 1910 November; 1 mounted photographic print
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 906
      Inscription on recto: "Hunting camp in Arizona"
    - View of a hunting camp with a wall tent, two women, and four men in Guadalupe Canyon, Arizona, 1910 November; 1 mounted photographic print
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 907
      Inscription on recto: "Our Camp in Guadaloupe Cañon, Arizona, Nov. 1910"
  - Kaibab National Forest
    - View of a herd of deer in Kaibab National Forest, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 119)
      Inscription on recto: "Kaibab Forest, Ariz."
      Ink stamp on verso: "Irwin's Studio, Silver City, New Mex."
  - Lee's Ferry
    - View of the Colorado River at Lee's Ferry, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 120)
      Inscription in negative: "Lees Ferry on the Colorado Riv., Northern Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of the Colorado River at Lee's Ferry, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 121)
      Inscription in negative: "Along the Colorado Riv. near Lees Ferry, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of the Colorado River at Lee's Ferry, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print, hand colored
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 908
  - Mission San José de Tumacácori
    - View of the Mission San José de Tumacácori on the Santa Cruz River in Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 photographic postcard (Box 2, Folder 122)
      Inscription in negative: "Tumacacori Mission on the Santa Cruz River, Ariz., Irwin"
  - Mission San Xavier del Bac
    - View of a door to Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, 1925; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - View of a door to Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, 1925; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Overhead view of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 125)
      Inscription in the negative: "San Xavier Mission, near Tucson, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 126)
      Ink stamp on verso: "16"
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, with buildings in the foreground, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, with buildings in the foreground, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, with donkeys and horse-drawn wagon in foreground, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, with two automobiles parked in front of it, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, with mountains in the distance, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, 1925; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 132)
      Inscription on verso: "1925"
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 133)
      Inscription on verso: "San Xavier Mission near Tucson, Ariz., one of the oldest missions in the U.S. Xavier (pronounced avier)"
    - View of Mission San Xavier del Bac near Tucson, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 134)
      Inscription in negative: "San Xavier Mission near Tucson, Ariz., Photo by Irwin"
  - Morenci
    - Overhead view of Morenci, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 135)
      Inscription in negative: "Morenci looking north"
  - Mormon Flat Dam
    - View of the Mormon Flat Dam on the Salt River in Arizona, 1929; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 136)
      Inscription in negative: "Dam along the Apache Trail, Ariz., © by Irwin Bro's""
  - Naco
    - Exterior portrait of two women posed standing with a United States army soldier next to an international boundary monument in Naco, Arizona, circa 1917; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 137)
      Inscription on recto: "Daisy and I, Naco, Arizona"
    - Exterior portrait of two women posed standing with two United States army soldiers next to an international boundary monument in Naco, Arizona, 1917; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 138)
      Inscription on verso: "Naco, 1917"
  - Needle's Eye
    - View of the Needle's Eye, an arch carved through a rock formation on the highway between Silver City and Clifton, New Mexico, with an automobile, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 909
      Inscription in negative: "The Needle's Eye, along the Silver City Clifton Highway, Photo by Irwin"
  - Nogales
    - View of Yucca gloriosa (Spanish dagger) plants near Nogales, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 139)
      Inscription on verso: "Spanish Dagger as it grows near Nogales, Arizona"
  - O.K. Ranch
    - View of a stream in Rucker Canyon at the O.K. Ranch, near Douglas, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 140)
      Inscription on recto: "Along the Rucker Canyon on the O.K. Ranch"
    - View of a cattle herd at the O.K. Ranch, near Douglas, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 141)
      Inscription on recto: "Scene on the O.K. Ranch in the foothills of the Chiricahua Mts."
    - View of horses at the O.K. Ranch, near Douglas, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 142)
      Inscription on recto: "Horses on O. K. Ranch, Douglas, Ariz."
  - Painted Desert
    - Overhead view of the Painted Desert near Holbrook, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 143)
      Inscription in negative: "Painted desert near Holbrook, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of petrified wood in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert near Holbrook, Arizona, circa 1904-1935; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 144)
      Inscription in negative: "In the petrified forest near Holbrook, Ariz., Irwin"
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 145)
      Ink stamp on verso: "A29"
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 2 unmounted photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print, hand colored
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 910
    - View of petrified wood and a desert landscape, probably in the petrified forest in the Painted Desert, Arizona, circa 1904-1945; 1 unmounted photographic print, hand colored
      Stored in: Oversize, Box 14, folder 911
  - Patagonia